♪ You're stuck in a time
warp from 2004 though ♪
♪ And I don't know what the
fuck that you rhyme for ♪
♪ You're pointless as Rapunzel
with fuckin' cornrows ♪
♪ You write normal?
Fuck being normal ♪
♪ And I just bought a new
raygun from the future ♪
♪ Just to come and shoot ya ♪
♪ Like when Fabolous
made Ray J mad ♪
♪ 'Cause Fab said he looked
like a fag at Mayweather's pad ♪
♪ Singin' to a man
while he played piano ♪
♪ Man, oh man, that
was a 24/7 special ♪
♪ On the cable channel ♪
♪ So Ray J went straight
to the radio station ♪
♪ The very next day ♪
♪ "Hey, Fab, I'ma kill you!" ♪
♪ Lyrics comin' at you
at supersonic speed ♪
♪ J.J. Fad ♪
♪ Uh, summa-lumma, dooma-lumma,
you assumin' I'm a human ♪
♪ What I gotta do to get it
through to you I'm superhuman ♪
♪ Innovative and
I'm made of rubber ♪
♪ So that anything you
say is ricochetin' ♪
♪ Off of me and it'll
glue to you and ♪
♪ I'm devastating, more
than ever demonstrating ♪
♪ How to give a
motherfuckin' audience ♪
♪ A feeling like it's
levitating, never fading ♪
♪ And I know that the
haters are forever waiting ♪
♪ For the day that they
can say I fell off ♪
♪ They'll be celebrating ♪
♪ 'Cause I know the way
to get 'em motivated ♪
♪ I make elevating music,
you make elevator music ♪
♪ "Oh, he's too mainstream." ♪
♪ Well, that's what they
do when they get jealous ♪
♪ They confuse it ♪
♪ "It's not hip hop, it's pop" ♪
♪ 'Cause I found a
hella way to fuse it ♪
♪ With rock, shock
rap with Doc ♪
♪ Throw on Lose Yourself
and make 'em lose it ♪
♪ "I don't know how to
make songs like that" ♪
♪ "I don't know
what words to use" ♪
♪ Let me know when
it occurs to you ♪
♪ While I'm rippin' any
one of these verses ♪
♪ That verses you ♪
♪ It's curtains, I'm
inadvertently hurtin' you ♪
♪ How many verses
I gotta murder to ♪
♪ Prove that if you
were half as nice ♪
♪ Your songs you could
sacrifice virgins too?! ♪
♪ Ugh, school
flunkie, pill junkie ♪
♪ But look at the accolades
these skills brung me ♪
♪ Full of myself,
but still hungry ♪
♪ I bully myself 'cause I make
me do what I put my mind to ♪
♪ And I'm a million
leagues above you ♪
♪ Ill when I speak in tongues ♪
♪ But it's still
tongue-in-cheek, fuck you ♪
♪ I'm drunk, so Satan,
take the fucking wheel ♪
♪ I'ma sleep in the front seat ♪
♪ Bumpin' Heavy D and the Boyz,
still "Chunky, but funky" ♪
♪ But in my head
there's something ♪
♪ I can feel tugging
and struggling ♪
♪ Angels fight with devils and ♪
♪ Here's what they
want from me ♪
♪ They're askin' me to eliminate
some of the women hate ♪
♪ But if you take
into consideration ♪
♪ The bitter hatred I have ♪
♪ Then you may be
a little patient ♪
♪ And more sympathetic
to the situation ♪
♪ And understand
the discrimination ♪
♪ But fuck it, life's
handin' you lemons? ♪
♪ Make lemonade then! ♪
♪ But if I can't
batter the women ♪
♪ How the fuck am I supposed
to bake them a cake then?! ♪
♪ Don't mistake him for Satan ♪
♪ It's a fatal mistake if you
think I need to be overseas ♪
♪ And take a vacation
to trip a broad ♪
♪ And make her fall
on her face and ♪
♪ Don't be a retard ♪
♪ Be a king? Think not ♪
♪ Why be a king when
you can be a God? ♪